<core:component xmlns:core="nova.component" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">

    <div class="row mt-3">
        <div class="col-4">
            <div class="d-flex-column ml-5">
                <p class="font-weight-bolder">ㅡ</p>
                <p class="font-weight-bolder text-start ">
                    Work Experience</p>
            </div>

        </div>
        <div class="col ">
            <div class="divider" />

            <div class="card mt-2 cardWidth">
                <div class="card-body ">
                    <h5 class="card-title font-weight-bold">Maventic / Software Developer</h5>
                    <h6 class="card-subtitle mb-2 font-weight-bold templatePrimaryColor">Jul 2018 - Dec 2020, Bangalore</h6>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Product based company.</li>
                        <li>Developed a standalone editor for building web applications with versatile functionality, capable of delivering end-to-end solutions.</li>
                        <li>Developed an Automation tool to CRUD in the database</li>
                        <li>Developed a SAP-PM Module (MOAST) mobile app.</li>
                        <li>Worked on openUI5 to create front end mobile applications</li>
                        <li>Developed applications for Android and IOS using Cordova</li>
                        <li>Developed custom controls in openUI5.</li>
                        <li>Wrote programs to handle client specific data for multiple devices.</li>
                        <li>Deployed java servers in aws</li>
                        <li>Developed and Maintained a Large Project which generated substantial revenue for the company.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <h6>Tech Stack : HTML, CSS ,Advance JavaScript, Typescript, OpenUI5, Cordova,Java, AWS EC2, Oracle Database, Postgres, Database Management, FCM</h6>
                </div>
            </div>


             <div class="card mt-2 cardWidth">
                <div class="card-body ">
                    <h5 class="card-title font-weight-bold">Atronas Aps, Denmark, Full Stack Engineer / Architect</h5>
                    <h6 class="card-subtitle mb-2 font-weight-bold templatePrimaryColor">2020 - Present</h6>
                    <ul>
                        <li>Built a cloud based enterprise level sass monitoring platform from scratch for SAP systems.</li>
                        <li>Worked and Managed 9-10 servers.</li>
                        <li>Architected the Entire Tech Stack.</li>
                        <li>Highly Scalable Architecture.</li>
                        <li>Worked on Multiple Technologies.</li>
                        <li>Solved Some Highly Complex Problems.</li>
                        <li>Architecture Built to Handle 10K concurrent Calls.</li>
                        <li>Response times are reduced to a few milliseconds regardless of Databases sizes (Usual Data Size contains 10GB+).</li>
                        <li>Frontend was built in React on top of Laravel.</li>
                        <li>Runs on Kubernetes cluster.</li>
                        <li>Servers are built as microservices so that it can be scaled.</li>
                        <li>Designed Alerts and Notification Architecture.</li>
                        <li>Designed to Monitor SAP System using a background job and notifies users on unexpected behaviors.</li>
                    </ul>
                    <h6>
                    Tech Stack : HTML, CSS, SASS, React, PHP, JavaScript, Python, Celery, Redis,
                        MySQL, Postgres, Dkron, Scheduler, Flask, Laravel Mix, Laravel, Docker, K8s,
                        RabbmitMQ, NodeJS, Puppeteer, Server Maintaince, Deployment, GitLab,
                        MongoDB, Nginx, LB, Gunicorn.
                    </h6>
                </div>
            </div>



        </div>
    </div>
</core:component>